clubflyers.com 2019-02-02

# Privacy Policy | Clubflyers.com | Printing | Inspiration | Magazine

This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 28, 2013.

Graphics, Type and Color Enterprises, Inc. (herein referred to as the “Clubflyers,” “we,” “us” or “our“) provides and makes available web sites located at clubflyers.com and clubflyersmag.com (the “Sites“ or "Site").  On our Sites we provide products, services, information, promotions and tools (collectively the "Service") to our Site visitors ("you" or "your"). 

Your privacy is very important to us. We developed this Privacy Policy to make sure you know what information we collect and how we use it. By using our Sites and the Service, you expressly consent to the collection, storage, disclosure and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy and you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use linked in the Sites, and incorporated herein by reference.

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace any part of this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. We may also, in the future, offer new services and/or features through the Sites or Service (including, the release of new tools and resources). Such new services and/or features shall be subject to the terms and conditions of the then current Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. You may read a current, effective copy of this Privacy Policy at any time by selecting the “Privacy Policy” link on the Sites. The revised terms and conditions will become effective at the time of posting. Your continued use of or access to the Sites or Service following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes acceptance of those changes. If any change to this Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, your sole remedy is to cease accessing, browsing and otherwise using the Site or Service.

To view the previous Privacy Policy, please click __**here.**__

**A. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

  * Website Visitors: We collect certain non-personally identifiable information through the use of web beacons, log files or various other technologies. Such information may include your IP address, browser type, site usage, and whether an email from us was opened, and other information that cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use the Sites and Service. This non-personally identifiable information may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and we may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents and business partners, or to other third parties for other lawful purposes. 
  * Cookies: A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our Sites and Services, and their website access preferences. You can delete cookies or prevent cookies from being stored on your computer by setting your browser to refuse cookies or to display a message when a cookie is being sent, with the drawback that certain features of our Sites and Service may not function properly without the aid of cookies. For more information on how your browser handles cookies, please refer to your particular browser's help section or other documentation.
  * Ads/ Promotions: Ads or promotions appearing on any of our Sites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by us and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
  * Information You Provide: You may provide us with certain personally identifiable information when you: 
    * register with a Site;
    * order products or gift certificates;
    * use the Services;
    * request customer support or send us any other communication;
    * sign up for newsletters or email alerts;
    * sign up for or redeem special offers, sweepstakes or contests; and/or
    * respond to surveys.

Such information may include your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, financial information, or other information relevant to Services, special offers, sweepstakes, contests and/or customer surveys. You may also provide us with information about other people, such as their email addresses, if you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the Sites, Services or promotions.

We do not disclose personally identifiable information other than as described below. You may also choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Sites or Services because such information may be required in order for you to register with a Site; purchase products or services; use Services, participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes; or initiate other transactions or communications with us.

  * Comments/Submissions: Through the Sites and Service, you will have the ability to upload content, post and share information about yourself and others, communicate with others and post comments or reviews of content found on or through the Service (collectively, “Your Submissions“). Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on publicly viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who views Your Submissions or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily submit, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personally identifiable information. Once you have posted information, you may not be able to edit or delete such information. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information included in Your Submissions.

**B. USE OF INFORMATION**

We use the personally identifiable information you provide to:

  * provide and improve the content, features and functionality of the Sites and Services;
  * improve our products and services;
  * better understand our users;
  * send you information about our products and services;
  * fulfill your requests for our products and services;
  * communicate with you about the status of your orders
  * respond to inquiries
  * provide notices about the Sites or Services
  * notify you of the results of sweepstakes, contest, and other promotions;
  * support our internal business purposes, such as data analysis, audits and so forth; and/or
  * communicate with you about your account. 

We use non-personally identifiable information to monitor the use and performance of the Site so that we can learn more about how people use the Site which helps us improve our products and services and significantly enhance your experience on our website.

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.

**C. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

We are not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your personally identifiable information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

  * Business Transfers: If Clubflyers, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired by or merged with another company, or in the unlikely event that we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Clubflyers may continue to use your personally identifiable information as set forth in this policy.
  * Related Companies: We may also share your personally identifiable information with our related companies, such as subsidiaries, parents, etc., for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.
  * Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other agents and trusted service providers and contractors to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases, processing payments and enhancing Site or Service features and functionality. In such cases, we require that these parties agree to use the information solely for the purpose for which we provided it to them and in accordance with our Privacy Policy.
  * Legal Requirements: Clubflyers may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate to: (i) comply with a legal obligation; (ii) comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders, government investigations, or other legal process; (iii) protect and defend the rights, property or safety of Clubflyers, our users, or others; (iv) investigate or respond to allegations of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other unlawful activity; or (v) protect against legal liability.
  * Children: We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personally identifiable information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you. We encourage parents and guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide personally identifiable information on or through the Sites or Service without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personally identifiable information to us through the Sites or Service, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

**D. INFORMATION SECURITY**

We use commercially reasonable and generally-accepted technological safeguards to protect any information we collect about you. The secure server software (SSL) we use encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, your account information on our Sites is password-protected for your privacy and security. You should always take steps to protect the confidentiality of the password you select. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.

We work very hard to protect your privacy, but we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee complete security. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to us through our Sites and Service.

Your personal data will be processed by us in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with us, you agree to this Privacy Policy and you consent to the transfer of all information you provide to us in the United States.

**E. OTHER WEBSITES AND SOCIAL MEDIA**

  * Links to Other Websites: You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Site. However, this Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. We have not reviewed and cannot control how third parties may use personally identifiable information you disclose to them, so you should carefully review the privacy policy of any third party website you visit before using it or disclosing your personally identifiable information to its provider.
  * Social Media: The Sites may include social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button and widgets, such as the “Share This” button or interactive mini-programs that run on the Sites. These features and widgets may collect your IP address, which pages and/or features you are visiting on the Sites and may set a cookie to enable the feature or widget to function properly. The widgets may also collect any information you supply to them directly, such as comments or other potentially personally identifiable information that you provide. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Sites. Your interactions with these features and widgets are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**F. ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

Much of your account information can be changed in the My Account section of the Sites. If you have any questions about what information is stored, what third parties, if any, it is shared with for direct marketing purposes, or would like to obtain a copy of such information, please contact us at:

DMCA@clubflyers.com  

Graphics, Type and Color Enterprises, Inc. 

Attn: Legal Department

2300 NW 7th Avenue  
Miami, FL  33127  
1-800-433-9298  

Subject to our ability to verify your identity, we will provide the information to you, and you may request that we delete or change any or all of the information.
